Guide to the Stanford University, Capital Planning and Management, Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University, Capital Planning and Management, records
1965-1992
SC0934
Stanford University. Capital Planning and Management
111 Linear feet (74 boxes)
The records include correspondence, reports, memoranda, and minutes largely pertaining to buildings, budgets, and facilities issues such as air quality and seismic refitting, with some files pertaining to personnel policies and issues.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Provenance
The records were received by the Stanford University Archives via administrative transfer in 2000.
Information about Access
The materials are open for research use.
Description of the Collection
The records include correspondence, reports, memoranda, and minutes largely pertaining to buildings, budgets, and facilities issues such as air quality and seismic refitting, with some files pertaining to personnel policies and issues. Many of these files were kept by Ray Bacchetti. In addition there are some files kept by Fernando de Necochea pertaining to El Centro Chicano, the Chicano Fellows Program, and Chicano research.
Access Terms
Bacchetti, Raymond F., 1934-; De Necochea, Fernando; Stanford University. Capital Planning and Management; Stanford University--Administration.
Collection Contents
- BOT (Board of Trustees) SSRL Concept, Mitchell Expansion 1986 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- BOT Academic Affairs and Development 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- BOT Pre-agenda 6/1986 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- BOT Concept Approval Mitchell Expansion 9/1985 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- BOT Committee on Finance and Administration 1985 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- BOT Pre-agenda 6/1985 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- BOT Pre-agenda 5/1985 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- BOT Pre-agenda 3/1985 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- BOT March Presentations (Box 1, Folder 9)
- BOT Pre-agenda 2/1985 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- BOT Pre-agenda 12/1984 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- BOT SSRL Project Approval 12/1984 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- BOT Pre-agenda 5/1984 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- BOT Mitchell Expansion Concept Approval 10/1983 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- BOT meeting 5/1984 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- BOT Pre-agenda 6/1984 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- BOT Pre-agenda 3/1984 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- BOT SSRL Project Approval 2/1984 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- BOT Pre-agenda 12/1983 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- BOT meeting 12/1983 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- BOT Pre-agenda 10/1983 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Facilities - Earthquakes General 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Facilities - Earthquakes Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Facilities - Earthquakes Buildings Studies (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Facilities - Earthquakes Action Group (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Facilities - Earthquakes Miscellaneous (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Facilities - Earthquakes 03-001 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Facilities - Earthquakes Knoll Structural Study (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Facilities - Earthquakes Lagunita Seismic Study (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Facilities - Quad 6 1987-1989 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Facilities - Quad 7 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Facilities - Museum (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Facilities - Stauffer Remodel (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Facilities - National Science Foundation Proposal (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Facilities - National Science Foundation Program (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Facilities - Quad 8 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Facilities - GSB (Graduate School of Business) Shear Walls (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Facilities - GSB Operations, Maintenance, Utilities (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Facilities - Quad 10 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Facilities - Quad 11 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Facilities - 11-002 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Facilities - 11-230 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Facilities - Quad 13 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Facilities - Quad 14 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Facilities - 14-50-170 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Facilities - 14-200 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Facilities - 14-270, 300, 640, 700 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Facilities - 14-830 Red Barn and Studios (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Facilities - 14-810 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Facilities - 14-810 Kiosk (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Facilities - 14-860/865/880 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Facilities - 14-905T (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Facilities - 14-930T (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Facilities - 14-940T, 950T (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Facilities - 14-960T Acacia (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Facilities - Parking Structure II (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Facilities - Parking Structure II (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Facilities - School of Education (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Facilities - Physics Tank Study (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Facilities - NWC (Near West Campus) Classrooms (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Facilities - NWC funding (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Facilities - Physics Tank (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Facilities - Roble Gym - New Theater (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Facilities - HEPL/SCA Superconductor Relocation Support (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Facilities - Memorial Church (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Facilities - Interim/New Electroplating Facility (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Facilities - Classroom Tour Report (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Bacchetti [Ray Bacchetti Vice Provost for Management and Director of University Budgets 1979-1988] - Stanford Review of Health and Safety 1988 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Bacchetti - Volunteer Convocation 10/16-18/1986 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Bacchetti - Development Seminar on University Governance 9/26/1986 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Bacchetti - ACUI Session Cancelled 6/1983 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Bacchetti - Humanities and Sciences Council 4/1983 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Bacchetti - Chinese Scientific Delegation 11/1978 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Bacchetti - Australia Speech 7/1978 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Bacchetti - CSU Budget Officers Remarks 3/1978 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Bacchetti - Dean of Student Affairs Staff Decision-making Remarks 3/1978 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Bacchetti - Cornell Consulting 5/1977 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Bacchetti - ALA Conference and Speech 6/1983 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Bacchetti - University Fellows 3/1983 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Bacchetti - Alumni Association Executive Board 2/1984 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Bacchetti - ASSU Course 1982-1985 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Bacchetti - AAUA Presentation 6/1979 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Bacchetti - AIR Meeting 5/1979 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Bacchetti - Stanford Today Column 7/1984 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Bacchetti - Annual Fund Volunteers 5/1984 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Bacchetti - National Resources Program 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Bacchetti - Stanford Associates 1984 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Bacchetti - California Independent Schools Conference 7/1981 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Bacchetti - ALA Collection Management Institute 1981 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Bacchetti - PAC-10 Student Conference 1/1981 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Bacchetti - Book Chapter - Financial Aid and Institutional Planning 1979 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- SU Annual Financial Reports, 1959-1983 (except 1976 and 1977) (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Facilities - Reforestation - Vegetation Management 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Facilities - NWC Outdoor Space Report 1988 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Facilities - ESF Incinerator Project 1988 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Facilities - Capital Budget Staff 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Facilities - Biological Sciences Building 1985-1987 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Facilities - Special Houses Financial Records (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Veronin (Valerie Veronin, Office of Vice President and Provost) - Chronological 1/1986-3/1988 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Facility Project and Planning Reports (Including NWC and General Use Permit draft) 1981-1986 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- SU Annual Financial Report 1985 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Operating Budget Guidelines 1985-1987 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Marguerite Study 1982 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Facilities - Budgets at Universities (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Handicapped Transition Plan 1979-1982 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Planned Maintenance Program 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Santa Clara General Use Permit 1988 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Management Development Program, Architect Questionaire (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Facilities - Academic Computing Facility (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Facilities - Task Force on Personnel Policies and Administration Report 1982 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Facilities - Budget Group Tour (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Facilities - CIS Operations and Management (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Facilities - Cost of Building Study 1979 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Facilities - Biological Sciences Lab Design Planning Study, Building Program 1984-1986 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Facilities - Biology Expansion Study (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Facilities - Articles (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Bacchetti - Tuition Stabilization Plan 1978 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- DAPER (Department of Athletics, Physical Education and Recreation) Geiger Meeting 1983 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- DAPER Stanford Athletic Board (SAB) (Box 6, Folder 5)
- DAPER Miscellaneous (Box 6, Folder 6)
- DAPER Fundraising Issues 1983-1984 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- DAPER Reserves (Box 6, Folder 8)
- DAPER Financial Data (Box 6, Folder 9)
- DAPER LRF (Long Range Forecast) 1985-1986 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- DAPER A-21 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- DAPER Coach Contracts (Box 6, Folder 12)
- DAPER Facilities General (Box 6, Folder 13)
- DAPER Maples Weight Room (Box 6, Folder 14)
- DAPER Campaign Planning (Box 6, Folder 15)
- DAPER LRF (Box 6, Folder 16)
- DAPER Buck Club (Box 6, Folder 17)
- DAPER Budget Restructure (Box 6, Folder 18)
- DAPER Dance (Box 6, Folder 19)
- DAPER Mahoney Report 1982-1983 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- DAPER School of Education (Box 6, Folder 21)
- DAPER SAB meeting 10/1981 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- DAPER SAB meetings through 5/1982 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- DAPER Finances (Box 6, Folder 24)
- DAPER Investments (Box 6, Folder 25)
- DAPER Scholarships Fund (Box 6, Folder 26)
- DAPER Audit (Box 6, Folder 27)
- DAPER Budget 1983-1985 (Box 6, Folder 28)
- DAPER Housing Loans (Box 6, Folder 29)
- *Removed Files* (Box 6, Folder 30)
- AICCU Financial Services Board Meeting Agendas (Box 6, Folder 31)
- AICCU Student Loans General (Box 6, Folder 32)
- AICCU Cohort Study (Box 6, Folder 33)
- Bacchetti - Budget 1985 (Box 6, Folder 34)
- CCBSP (Cabinet Committee on Budget and Strategic Planning) 9/1991 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- CCBSP Repositioning Plan to Budget Reductions 1990 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- CCBSP Repositioning Steering Committee 3/1990 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Vice President Initiative Report 9/5/1991 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Personnel Information Publications (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Facilities - Special Houses Chronological 1985-1991 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Multiculturalism and Minorities Publications (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Facilities - Strategic Planning 1992 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Budget - Operating Budget Guidelines 1990-1992 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Budget - Budget Reduction 1992 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Administrative Reorganization 1990-1991 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- HRPS (Human Resources Policy Staff) 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- HR (Human Resources) Retreat 1989 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- HR Strategic Plan 1989 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- HR Rob Parker Information Resources Presentation 5/1988 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- HR UCMI (University Commission on Minority Issues) Ethnic Staff Groups Meeting (Box 8, Folder 1)
- HR UCMI Minorities in the Classroom (Box 8, Folder 2)
- HR Chart and Statement (Box 8, Folder 3)
- HR Rob Parker CUPA and MGU material 10/1988 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- HR Inventory of Programs 1984-1988 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- HR Meeting 8/1990 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- HR Administrative Council (Box 8, Folder 7)
- HR Staff Retreat 10/1989 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- HRPS Information 1989-1990 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- HR Action Team Final Report 1990 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- HR Personnel Function Proposed Design 1986 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- HRPS 11/1988-7/1990 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- HR 1988 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Special Houses Financial Records 1984-1985 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- GPI (General Plan Improvement Program) (Box 8, Folder 15)
- GPI Working Group (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Landscape Design Guidelines 1989 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Main Quad Restoration Study 2/1988 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Hanna House 1989-1990 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Earthquake Risk Management Commission (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Miscellaneous Reports: Admissions and Financial Aid, DAPER plan, Sign Plan, Oak Regeneration 1987-1988, Centennial Campaign, Asbestos Abatement 1986, Regional Planning 1987-1989, Circulation Plan 1988 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- Facilities - Field House and Old Pavilion (Box 9, Folder 1)
- HR UCMI Budget 1989 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Office of Management and Budget - Projecting University Debt Ratings Report 1985 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Office of Management and Budget - Miscellaneous (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Office of Management and Budget - NWC Redevelopment Project (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Campus Center Goals (Box 9, Folder 6)
- CIV (Cultures, Ideas and Values) Course Articles 1988-1989 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- CIV Press Releases (Box 9, Folder 8)
- CIV Syllabi 1985-1989 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- CIV Attachments (Box 9, Folder 10)
- CIV Faculty Opinion On Area 1 Requirement (Box 9, Folder 11)
- CIV Student Opinion On Area 1 Requirement (Box 9, Folder 12)
- CIV Outside Opinions (Box 9, Folder 13)
- CIV Task Force Member Proposals (Box 9, Folder 14)
- CIV Articles 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- CIV Clippings 1987-1988 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- de Nechochea (Fernando de Nechochea, Assistant Provost/Advisor to President on Mexican American Affairs) - Center for Research in International Affairs 1981 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- de Nechochea - Project on U.S.-Mexico Relations (Box 9, Folder 18)
- de Nechochea - Advisor to President on Chicano Affairs 1986 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Chicano Fellows Program 1980-1987 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Chicano Fellows Program 1975-1981 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Chicano Fellows Program Redefinition Proposal 1986 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Chicano Fellows Program Library Planning Committee (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Chicano Graduation 1979-1990 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- CGSA (Chicano Graduate Student Association) (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Chicano Interim Executive Committee (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Chicano/Latino Orientation 1979-1990 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Air Quality - Ambient (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Air Quality - Bio-Chem Quad (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Air Quality - McCullough (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Air Quality - Mitchell Re-entrainment Study (Box 10, Folder 11)
- ESF (Environmental Safety Facility) Planning (Box 10, Folder 12)
- ESF Chemical Stores (Box 10, Folder 13)
- ESF Incinerator Test Results 12/1987 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- ESF Re-entrainment Corrections (Box 10, Folder 15)
- ESF Pre-design Study Final Report (Box 10, Folder 16)
- ESF Re-entrainment Study Final Report (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Regional Planning 1987-1988 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- NWC Quarterly Communication 1989 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- NWC Program Statement 1985 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- DAPER Plan 9/1987 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Emergency Response Plan (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Proposed Operating Budget 1972-1973 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Operating Budget Guidelines 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Annual Financial Report 1987 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Indirect Cost Study 1982 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Budget Cost Plan, Adamson and Associates 1987 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Insurance and Risk Management Report 1988 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Budget and Operations Miscellaneous (Box 11, Folder 9)
- SU Business Plan (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Budget - Tuition Income Estimates 1982 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Budget - Student Loans (Box 11, Folder 12)
- DAPER Master Planning of East and West Regions (Box 11, Folder 13)
- DAPER Admissions (Box 11, Folder 14)
- DAPER NCAA Compliance (SU Audits) 1983 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- DAPER Football Coaches 1986 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- DAPER Maples Trust 1983 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- DAPER COIN and other housing correspondence (Box 11, Folder 18)
- DAPER Golf Course Operations December 1982 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- DAPER Endowed Coaches (Box 11, Folder 20)
- DAPER Dance Division (Box 11, Folder 21)
- DAPER Koppett Articles 10/1983 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- DAPER De Guerre Fund 1981-1982 (Box 11, Folder 23)
- DAPER De Guerre Plaza (Box 11, Folder 24)
- DAPER Buck Club Audit 2/1984 (Box 11, Folder 25)
- DAPER Regular Meetings (DK, AG, AC, RFB) 1980-1983 (Box 11, Folder 26)
- DAPER Fundraising (Box 11, Folder 27)
- DAPER Plans and Special Arrangements Investment Fund (Box 11, Folder 28)
- DAPER CAPER Committee (Box 11, Folder 29)
- DAPER CAPER, SAP etc. Miscellaneous 1985- (Box 11, Folder 30)
- DAPER Buck Club Separately Investing Funds (Box 11, Folder 31)
- DAPER Management Planning 1980 (Box 11, Folder 32)
- DAPER Grounds Operations and Management 1979 (Box 11, Folder 33)
- DAPER RFB Liaison (Box 11, Folder 34)
- DAPER Personnel (Box 11, Folder 35)
- DAPER Scholarships (Box 11, Folder 36)
- DAPER Supplementary Compensation (Box 11, Folder 37)
- DAPER Old Pavilion Valuation (Box 11, Folder 38)
- DAPER Interest Income and Banking Arrangements (Box 11, Folder 39)
- DAPER Meetings with DK, JPS, FAG (AC and RFB) (Box 11, Folder 40)
- DAPER Reserves (Box 11, Folder 41)
- DAPER Student Aid Cost Avoidance (Box 11, Folder 42)
- DAPER Audit 1981 (Box 11, Folder 43)
- DAPER BOT Meeting 10/10/1983 (Box 11, Folder 44)
- DAPER BOT Meeting Preparation 12/1983 (Box 11, Folder 45)
- DAPER CAPER Volleyball Review (Box 11, Folder 46)
- DAPER CAPER 1983-1984 (Box 11, Folder 47)
- DAPER Interface with Controller and other Auxiliaries (Box 11, Folder 48)
- DAPER Tom Davis 1986 (Box 11, Folder 49)
- DAPER Andy Geiger articles 1985 (Box 11, Folder 50)
- DAPER Personnel Matters (Box 11, Folder 51)
- DAPER Financial (Box 11, Folder 52)
- DAPER Women's Financial Aid (Box 11, Folder 53)
- DAPER Development Meetings (Box 11, Folder 54)
- DAPER Agendas and Miscellaneous (Box 11, Folder 55)
- DAPER Faculty and Staff Benefits Pool (Box 11, Folder 56)
- DAPER A-21 Issues (Box 11, Folder 57)
- DAPER Miscellaneous (Box 11, Folder 58)
- DAPER Philosophy Statement (Box 11, Folder 59)
- DAPER Funding Philosophy (Box 11, Folder 60)
- DAPER Budget Presentation (Box 11, Folder 61)
- DAPER Budget 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 62)
- DAPER LRF (Box 11, Folder 63)
- DAPER Monthly Financial Reports (Box 11, Folder 64)
- Budget - Indirect Cost Study 1986-1987 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Budget - Migration Analysis (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Advanced Materials Research Building Schematic Design and Architectural Program, Anderson DeBartolo Pan 1988 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- NWC Planning Staff Working Agendas 1989 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- NWC Planning Group Academic Program 1986 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- NWC Project Management Plan 1985 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- GPI (General Plant Improvement) Program 1986-1987 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Insurance and Risk Management Report 1985 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- SU Annual Financial Report 1986 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Operations and Maintenance Service Center Budgets 1986-1987 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Reports on Athletics Plan, Elbasani and Logan 1987 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Budget - Allocation by Formula, School of Medicine 1985 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Regional Planning 1986-1987 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- DAPER Regional Plan, Growing Region 1987 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- NWC Architects Collaborative on Connective Elements Vol.1 Outdoor Spaces 1988 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- NWC Architects Collaborative on Connective Elements Vol. 2 Arcades (Box 13, Folder 1)
- NWC Academic Program 1986 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- NWC Academic Program School Supplemental Background 1986 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- NWC Cost Model (Box 13, Folder 4)
- NWC Working Partners (Box 13, Folder 5)
- NWC Phase II Program 1986 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Facilities - Tresidder Memorial Union Project 1985 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Facilities - Regional Planning of SU Campus 9/1987 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Facilities - Keck Science Building Post-Occupancy Evaluation (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Facilities - High Tech Facilities Conference 1987 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Facilities - Facility Project Review Process BOT Report 1981 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Budget 1983-1984 - Admissions (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Budget 1983-1984 - Business and Finance (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Budget 1983-1984 - DAPER (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Budget 1983-1984 - Dean of Student Affairs (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Budget 1983-1984 - Development (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Budget 1983-1984 - Education (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Budget 1983-1984 - Earth Sciences (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Budget 1983-1984 - Engineering (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Budget 1983-1984 - Undergraduate Financial Aid (Box 13, Folder 20)
- Budget 1983-1984 - Graduate Studies (Box 13, Folder 21)
- Budget 1983-1984 - Graduate School of Business (Box 13, Folder 22)
- Budget 1983-1984 - Hoover Institution (Box 13, Folder 23)
- Budget 1983-1984 - Humanities and Science (Box 13, Folder 24)
- Budget 1983-1984 - Independent Labs (Box 13, Folder 25)
- Budget 1983-1984 - ITS (Formerly SCIT, SCIP) (Box 13, Folder 26)
- Budget 1983-1984 - Law School (Box 13, Folder 27)
- Budget 1983-1984 - Libraries (Box 13, Folder 28)
- Budget 1983-1984 - Medicine (Box 13, Folder 29)
- Budget 1983-1984 - Memorial Church/Chapel (Box 13, Folder 30)
- Budget 1983-1984 - Overseas Studies (Box 13, Folder 31)
- Budget 1983-1984 - President/Provost's Office (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Budget 1983-1984 - University Press (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Budget 1983-1984 - Public Affairs (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Budget 1983-1984 - Registrar (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Budget 1983-1984 - SLAC (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Budget 1983-1984 - Summer Session (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Budget 1983-1984 - University Council (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Budget 1983-1984 - Western Culture Program (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Personnel Task Force (Task Force on Personnel, Policies and Administration) Policies 1982-1983 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Personnel Task Force Decentralization (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Personnel Task Force Implementation (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Personnel Task Force Assessment of Recommendations 1983 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Personnel Task Force Final Report 1982 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Personnel Task Force Black Concerns (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Personnel Task Force Chicano concerns (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Investment Committee Annual Report on Gift Real Estate 1985 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Investment Committee Policy 1983 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- Indirect Costs Task Force 1984 (Box 14, Folder 18)
- Indirect Costs Rates 1985-1986 (Box 14, Folder 19)
- Operations and Maintenance Planned Maintenance 1983 (Box 14, Folder 20)
- Budget - Salary Planning 1985-1986 (Box 14, Folder 21)
- Budget - Proposed Budget 1968/69-1973/74 (Box 14, Folder 22)
- Budget - Budget Protocols 1981-1982 (Box 14, Folder 23)
- Budget - Budget Request Letters 1981-1982 (Box 14, Folder 24)
- Budget - Capital Budget Staff - Meetings 1986-1987 (Box 14, Folder 25)
- Budget - Capital Budget Staff - Meetings 1987-1988 (Box 14, Folder 26)
- Budget - Capital Budget Staff - Meetings 1988-1989 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Budget - Medical School Financial Schedules 1984 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Budget - Medical Center Regional Planning Report 1986 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Future Academic Programs and Resource Needs of the Clinical (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Walkthroughs on EE, Varian/HEPL, Material Science, Comp. Science, Statistics, Chemistry, Chemical Engineering, Applied Physics 1984 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- VPPM (Vice Provost for Planning and Management) Senior Staff Meeting Agenda 3/1991 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- VPPM Senior Staff Meetings 1-6/1991 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- VPPM Senior Staff Meetings 7-9/1991 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Annual Review Panel Report on Stanford's Multiracial, Multicultural Community 1991 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Final Report of the Annual Review Panel - Staff Survey on Minority Issues and General Job Satisfaction 8/1990 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Housing Commission Report 1991 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Report on Administrative Reorganization 9/1990 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Consulting Inventory 1990 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- NWC Bacchetti Chronology 1986 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Hopkins Marine Station Regional Planning 1991 (Box 15, Folder 15)
- Arboretum Regional Plan (Box 15, Folder 16)
- Energy Efficiency Concerns 1991 (Box 15, Folder 17)
- BOT Design Guidelines (Box 15, Folder 18)